A Guide to the Fries Textile Plant Records, 1900-1988
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series II: Correspondence, 1901-1958
  - Barrett Changer Company. Chicago, Ill., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - The Barrett Co, 36th and Rays Ferry Ave, Philadelphia, 1918-1921 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Bartholomew Hardwood Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Bates Mfg. Co., Orange N.J., 1920 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Baumgarten and Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Baumgarten and Co., Baltimore, Md., 1918-1920 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Beach Mfg. Co., Montrose, Pa., 1920 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - R.H. Beaumont Co? 344 Arch Street Philadelphia PA, 1920 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Wm and Chas Beck, 1919-1920 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Becker-Moore Paint Co, St. Louis, Mo, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Beckwith Machinery Co, Pittsburgh Pa., 1920-1921 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - A.G. Belden and Co, New York, 1918-1921 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Belknap Hdwe. and Mfg. Co., 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Belknap Hdwe. and Mfg. Co, Louisville, KY., 1918-1921 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Belmont Iron Works, Philadelphia, Pa., 1919-1920 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Bemis Bro. Bag Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Berry-Roberts Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - L. Best Co., 28-30 West Broadway, New York City., 1920 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Billings and Spencer Co, Hartford Conn., 1920 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Binney and Smith, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Binswanger Co, Richmond Va, 1918-1920 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Bird and Son, East Walpole, Mass., 1920 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Bird-Wilcox Co., Atlanta, Ga., 1918-1920 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - Blackstone Mutual Fire Ins. Co., 1921 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - Blackstone Mutual Fire Ins. Co. Providence R.I., 1920-1921 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - Blackstone Mutual Fire Insurance Co. Providence, R.I., 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - Blaw-Knox Co., 1919 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - W.A. Blonck and Co. Chicago, Ill., 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - Bloomfield Labor Digest. 6 Beacon St. Boston, Mass., 1920 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - Bluefield Coal and Coke Co., 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Bluefield Coal and Coke Co., Bluefield, W. Va., 1918-1921 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Bluefield Hardware Co., Bluefield, W. Va., 1919-1920 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Blumenfield Co, Memphis Tenn., 1920 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Blueridge Printing Co., 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - Bodine Stone Co, Buffalo Station Va., 1918 (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Mr. A.J. Booker, C/O Citizens Bank, Blackstone, Va., 1919 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - B.F. Bond Paper Co. Baltimore MD, 1918-1920 (Box 32, Folder 56)
  - Bonsack Woolen Mill, Roanoke, Va., 1920 (Box 32, Folder 57)
  - Mrs. R.C. Boothe, Pulaski, Va., 1919 (Box 32, Folder 58)
  - Bosworth Bag Co, Memphis Tenn., 1918-1921 (Box 32, Folder 59)
  - The Bougham Stationary Co, Richmond Va., 1918 (Box 32, Folder 60)
  - Henry Bower Chemical Mfg. Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 61)
  - Braid Elec. Co., 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 62)
  - Briggs-Shaffner Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 63)
  - Briggs Shaffner Winston-Salem, 1919-1921 (Box 32, Folder 64)
  - Bristol Door and Lumber Co., 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 65)
  - Bristol Door and Lumber Co, Bristol Tenn, 1919-1921 (Box 32, Folder 66)
  - Bristol Typewrighter Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 67)
  - Bristol Typewriter Co, Bristol Va, 1918-1920 (Box 32, Folder 68)
  - Broderick and Bascom Rope Co., St. Louis, Mo., 1919 (Box 32, Folder 69)
  - Bronx Company New York City, 1920 (Box 32, Folder 70)
  - J. Brooksbank Son and Co., 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 71)
  - The David Brown Co., Lawrence, Mass., 1919 (Box 32, Folder 72)
  - Frank E. Brown, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 73)
  - Frank E. Brown Roanoke, Va, 1919-1921 (Box 32, Folder 74)
  - Brown Instrument Co., 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 75)
  - Brown and Sharpe Mfg. Co., Providence, R.I., 1919-1921 (Box 32, Folder 76)
  - T.E. Bruce (Scottsville Drug Co.), 1922 (Box 32, Folder 77)
  - Budd-Piper Roofing Co., 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 78)
  - Budd-Piper Roofing Co., Durham, N.C., 1921 (Box 32, Folder 79)
  - Buff and Buff Mfg. Co., Boston, Mass., 1919 (Box 32, Folder 80)
  - Buffalo Steam Pump Co., Buffalo, N.Y., 1920-1921 (Box 32, Folder 81)
  - Buffalo Steam Pump Co, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 82)
  - Buffalo Steel Co., Towanda, N.Y., 1919 (Box 32, Folder 83)
  - Buffalo Wire Works Co., 1921 (Box 32, Folder 84)
  - Building Supplies Corp., 1921-1922 (Box 32, Folder 85)
  - Building Supplies Corp., Richmond Va., 1918-1921 (Box 32, Folder 86)
  - R. McC. Bullington and Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 87)
  - Burdett Oxygen Co, Chicago, Ill., 1918 (Box 32, Folder 88)
  - Burlington Coal Co., Cincinnati, Ohio., 1918 (Box 32, Folder 89)
  - Burrell Belting Co, Chicago Ill, 1921 (Box 32, Folder 90)
  - The Burt Mfg. Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 91)
  - The Burt Mfg. Co., Akron, Ohio., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 92)
  - Bury Compressor Co., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 93)
  - A.M. Byers Co., Pittsburg, Pa., 1919 (Box 32, Folder 94)
  - C.W. Byrd, Durham, N.C., 1922 (Box 32, Folder 95)
  - C-T "Letters" Binders, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 96)
  - Unemployment Compensation Comm., 1947 (Box 32, Folder 97)
  - Universal Winding Co.; UpJohn Co; US Ring Traveler Comp.; C.L Upchurch and Sons, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 98)
  - US. Govt: Depts. of Labor, Agriculture, Commerce, and Interior; Post Office Dept; House and Senate, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 99)
  - Miscellaneous V's, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 100)
  - Commonwealth of Va. Department of Health, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 101)
  - Va. Industrial Commission; Division of Purchasing and Printing; State Board of Education; Dept. of Highways; Dept. of Agric.; Division of Motor Vehicles, 1947 (Box 155, Folder 36)
  - Va. School Equipment Co.; Va. Manufacturing Association, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 103)
  - Va. Scrap Iron and Metal; Vogel Peterson Co; Wallace and Tiernan Comp; Warner and Swasey Co., 1947 (Box 32, Folder 104)
  - Va. State Chamber of Commerce; Va. State Wide Safety Conference, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 105)
  - Veeder-Root Inc.; Vaughan Bassett Furniture Comp.; Victor Ring Traveler Comp., 1947 (Box 32, Folder 106)
  - Miscellaneous W's, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 107)
  - Robert W. Walters Supply Co.; Watson and Desmond, Special Reps; Western Carloading Co.; West Disinfecting Co., 1947 (Box 32, Folder 108)
  - Westinghouse Electric and Supply, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 109)
  - Whitin Machine Works, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 110)
  - D.E. Whiton Machine Comp; Troy Whitehead Machinery Comp; J.H. Windle and Co., 1947 (Box 32, Folder 111)
  - YMCA, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 112)
  - Miscellaneous A's, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 113)
  - Amer. Cotton Manf. Assoc.; Aldrich Machine Works; Addressograph Sales Agency; Adams and Tate, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 114)
  - American Monorail Co., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - App. Elec. Power; Anderson, Clayton, and Co.; Amsterdam Printing Co; Amer. Floor Products, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Atlas Supply Co; Atlanta Brush Co.; Ashworth Bros; Armstrong Cork Comp, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - A.W. Cash Co; C. Grady Cates; Carolina Bagging Co; Charlotte Supply Co, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous "B" file, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Bachman Uxbridge Worsted Corp; Bahan Textile Machinery Co; Barber Coleman Comp.; Baush and Lomb Optical Co, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - The Bahnson Company, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Bahnson, Spaugh, Reid, Tulloch, etc (intraplant memos), 1949 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - John Bayne and Co; Everett Beasley; Belk's Department Store; Belknap Hardware Co., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Bemis Bro. Bag Co; Wesly Bintz; WS Balden Co; A.P. Bond Paper Co., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Burlington Truckers; Butler Iron and Steele; Carolina Specialty Co; R.L. Carper Co., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous "C" File, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Chase Bay Co.; Chicago Pharmacal Co; Clipper Mfg. Co., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Corn Products Sales Co., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Currier-Withers Supply Co; Cotton Textile Institute Inc; Cone FInishing Co., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Curtis and Marble Machine Co; Cutler's Exchange, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous D file, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - D. Brown Co.; Brunswick-Balke Collender Co, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Dillard Paper Co; J. Dashew Inc; Dan River Mills, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Dixon Lubricating Saddle Co; Dillon Supply Co; Dixie Bag Co, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Drake Corporation; Draper Corporation, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous E file, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Elliot Service Co; Engineering Sales Co, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - The Esterline-Angus Co., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous F, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - JT Beatty Machine Comp, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - M.M. Basworth Co; Cleveland Bowser Jr.; Brenner Iron and Supply Co.; Brooks Transportation C., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Seabrook Transmission Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Security Life and Trust Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Service Appliance Co., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Service Storage and Transfer Co., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Seydel-Woolley and Co, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Sherwin-Williams Co., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Signode Steel Strapping Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - SIPP-Eastwood Corporation, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Slaughter Machinery Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - S. Morgan Smith Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Snow Lumber Co., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Socony-Vacuum Oil Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Sonoco Products Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Southern Bobbin Works, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Southern Electric Service Company, Inc., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Southern Loom-Reed Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Steel Heddle Mfg. Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Stowe-Woodward, Inc., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Gus Suckow Jr, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Superior-Sterling Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Sykes Foundry and Machine Co., Inc., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous T, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Taylor Instrument Companies, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Terrell Machine Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Texize Chemicals, Inc, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Textile Fibre Spray, Inc., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - The Textile Mill Supply Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Textile Paper Products, Inc, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - Textile Specialty Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Ton-Tex Corp., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Traffic Dept., January- March 1955 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Traffic Dept., April-June 1955 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Traffic Dept, July- September 1955 (Box 33, Folder 60)
  - Traffic Dept, October- December 1955 (Box 33, Folder 61)
  - Turner Brothers, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 62)
  - Miscellaneous U, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 63)
  - United Iron and Metal Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 64)
  - United States Rubber Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 65)
  - US Bobbin and Shuttle Co., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 66)
  - US Dept of Agriculture, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 67)
  - US Dept. of Commerce, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 68)
  - US Dept of Labor, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 69)
  - US Government Federal Power Commission, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 70)
  - US Senate, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 71)
  - US Treasury Dept, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 72)
  - Miscellaneous V, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 73)
  - Valley Bag Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 74)
  - Veeder-Root Inc., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 75)
  - Vickers Inc., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 76)
  - Victor Ring Traveler Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 77)
  - Commonwealth of Va Advisory Legislative Council, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 78)
  - Va Chamber of Commerce, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 79)
  - Commonwealth of Va Corporation Commission, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 80)
  - Va Council on Health and Medical Care, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 81)
  - Commonwealth of Va Dept. of Health (Box 33, Folder 82)
  - Commonwealth of Va Dept of Highways, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 83)
  - Commonwealth of Va Industrial Commission, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 84)
  - Commonwealth of Va Dept. of Labor and Industry, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 85)
  - Commonwealth of Va Dept of Public Welfare, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 86)
  - Commonwealth of Va Dept of Taxation, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 87)
  - Commonwealth of Va Division of Water Works, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 88)
  - Va Manufacturers Association, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 89)
  - Va Medical College, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 90)
  - Commonwealth of Va Ports Authority, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 91)
  - The Va Society for Crippled Children and Adults, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 92)
  - Commonwealth of Va State Board of Education, 1952-1955 (Box 33, Folder 93)
  - Commonwealth of Va Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 94)
  - Miscellaneous W, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 95)
  - Waukesha Foundry Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 96)
  - Washington Mills Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 97)
  - Watson and Desmond, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 98)
  - Werthan Bag Corporation, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 99)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 100)
  - Whitin Machine Works, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 101)
  - Whitinsville Spinning Ring Company, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 102)
  - Williams and Shelton Company, Inc., 1955 (Box 33, Folder 103)
  - Wilson Lewith, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 104)
  - Mr. H.D. Winter, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 105)
  - Miscellaneous X, Y, Z, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 106)
  - YMCA (John Thorpe), 1955 (Box 33, Folder 107)
  - YMCA, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 108)
  - Miscellaneous A, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - ABC Alperin Dry Goods Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Abington Textile Machinery Works, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Inc, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - American Associated Consultants, Inc., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - American Cotton Manufacturers Institute, Inc., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - American Pigment Corporation, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - American Steel Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Clayton, and Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Anderson, Clayton, and Flemming, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Appalachian Electric Power Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Armstrong Cork Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Arrow Steamship Lines, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Ashworth Bros Inc., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Associated Transport Inc., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Atlanta Brush Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Atlantic India Rubber Works, Inc., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Atlas Supply Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous B, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Bahan Textile Machinery Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - The Bahnson Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Baker-Cockrell Agency, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Mrs. Warren M. Ballard, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Barber-Colman Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - John Bayne and Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Belk-Settle Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Bemis Bro. Bag Co., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - F.W. Berry Produce, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - James G. Biddle Co., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - John P. Bing M.D., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Boiler Brick and Refractory Co., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Borne Scrymser Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Brown Grease Gun Co - (W.M. Parsley Agent), 1956 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Paul D. Brown and Associates, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - H.P. Burnett, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous C, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Carolina Bagging Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Carolina Specialty Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - R.L. Carper Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - C. Grady Cates, Inc., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Celanese Corporation of America, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Chemical Processing Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Chiswick Electric Motor Co., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - C.E. Clarke and Sons, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Mrs. Homer Clemens, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Comer Machinery Co., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Cone Mills Corporation, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Congress Factors Corporation, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Corn Products Sales Co., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - E.F. Craven Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Crystal Springs Bleachery, Inc., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Curtis and Marble Machine Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous D, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Mr. C.W. Davidson, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Dept. of Public Welfare, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Diehl Manufacturing Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Dixie Loom Reed Co., 1956 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Dixon Corporation, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Draper Corporation, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Draper Manufacturing Company, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Duke Hospital, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Miscellaneous E, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - General Motor Lines, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Pyrene - C-O-Two Division, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Miscellaneous 'A', 1957 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Abington Textile Machinery Works, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Acme Steel Co., 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Acme Textile Mill Ends, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Addressograph-Multigraph Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - Allen Morrison Sign Co. Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Allen Thorton Corp., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 71)
  - Anderson, Clayton and Fleming, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 72)
  - America Cotton Mfrs. Inst. Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 73)
  - American Moistening Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 74)
  - Appalachian Electric Power Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 75)
  - Armco Drainage and Metal Products, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 76)
  - Armstrong Cork Company, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 77)
  - Arrow Lines, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 78)
  - Ashworth Bros., Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 79)
  - Aspden Associates Inc. Greensboro (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - Atlantic Refining Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 81)
  - Atlas Supply Co. Winston-Salem, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 82)
  - Aust Motor Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 83)
  - The Austrian Trade Delegate, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 84)
  - Miscellaneous "B", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 85)
  - Bahan Textile Machinery Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 86)
  - Barber-Colman Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 87)
  - John Bayne and Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 88)
  - Belk Stores, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 89)
  - Borne Chemical Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 90)
  - Brady Mfg. Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 91)
  - Brown Grease Gun Co. W.M. Parsley, Agent, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 92)
  - Mr. James H. Brown, Jr., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 93)
  - Buccaneer Line, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 94)
  - Buffalo Fire Appliance Corp., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 95)
  - Buffalo Forge Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 96)
  - A.S. Burg Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 97)
  - Mrs. John D. Burnett, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 98)
  - Miscellaneous "C", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 99)
  - Carolina Specialty Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 100)
  - Carroll County - Dept. of Public Welfare, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 101)
  - Celanese Corporation of America, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 102)
  - Chemical Processing Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 103)
  - Chicopee Mfg. Corp., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 104)
  - Mr. James Arthur Coleman, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 105)
  - C-O Two Division, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 106)
  - Corn Product Sales Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 107)
  - E.F. Craven Company, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 108)
  - Curtis and Marble Machine Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 109)
  - Miscellaneous "D", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 110)
  - D. and S. Engineering Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 111)
  - Davis and Catterall, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 112)
  - The Dayton Rubber Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 113)
  - Diehl Manufacturing Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 114)
  - Dixie Loom Reed Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 115)
  - Dixie Spindle and Flyer Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 116)
  - The Dobeckmun Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 117)
  - Draper Corporation, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 118)
  - Miscellaneous "E", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 119)
  - Electric Service and Sales Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 120)
  - Electric Furnace Corp., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 121)
  - The Electric Storage Battery Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 122)
  - The Electro-Hercules Steel Co, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 123)
  - Mr. F. L. Elkins, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 124)
  - Ely and Walker, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 125)
  - Miscellaneous "F", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 126)
  - Factory Insurance Association, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 127)
  - Federal Compress and Warehouse Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 128)
  - Ferguson Gear Company, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 129)
  - Finnell System, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 130)
  - First National Bank Fries, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 131)
  - Fisher Governor Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 132)
  - Fiske-Carter Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 133)
  - FX Lab Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 134)
  - Town of Fries, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 135)
  - Miscellaneous "G", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 136)
  - General Coal Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 137)
  - General Motor Lines, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 138)
  - Edwin F. Glenn, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 139)
  - Globe Mills Company, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 140)
  - Goldens Foundry and Machine Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 141)
  - Bill G. Goldston, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 142)
  - Gossett Machine Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 143)
  - Grayson County Officials, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 144)
  - Grinnell Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 145)
  - Hobert N. Grubb, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 146)
  - The Guider Specialty Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 147)
  - Miscellneous "H", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 148)
  - Hall's Textile Machinery Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 149)
  - Hanes Dye and Finishing Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 150)
  - Hasler-Tel Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 151)
  - Hennis Freight Lines, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 152)
  - Holiday Sprinkler Corp., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 153)
  - R.E.L. Holt, Jr. and Associates, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 154)
  - H.I. Hopper, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 155)
  - Hospital Savings Association, 1957 (Box 155, Folder 37)
  - Mr. H.G. Hudson Ratcliff, Vaughn, Hudson, Ferrell and Carter, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 157)
  - Miscellaneous I", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 158)
  - Ideal Machine Shops, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 159)
  - Industrial Fine Protection Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 160)
  - Inter-Mountain Coals, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 161)
  - Island Creek Coal Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 162)
  - Miscellaneous "J", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 163)
  - Jenkins Metal Shops, Inc., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 164)
  - W.W. Johnson, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 165)
  - Miscellaneous "K", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 166)
  - The Keever Starch Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 167)
  - Kemble-Cochran Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 168)
  - Keystone Electric Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 169)
  - Ansel E. King, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 170)
  - Kingsport Electric Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 171)
  - Earl E. Knox Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 172)
  - Miscellaneous "L", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 173)
  - Lambeth Rope Corp., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 174)
  - Lee Engineering Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 175)
  - The James Leffel and Co., 1957 (Box 34, Folder 176)
  - Leslie, April 1957 (Box 34, Folder 177)
  - Leslie, May 1957 (Box 34, Folder 178)
  - Leslie and Company, June 1957 (Box 34, Folder 179)
  - Leslie and Co., July 1957 (Box 34, Folder 180)
  - Leslie and Co., September 1957 (Box 34, Folder 181)
  - Leslie, Catlin and Co Inc., October 1957 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Leslie and Co., August 1957 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Leslie, Catlin and Co. Inc., November 1957 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Leslie, Catlin and Co. Inc., December 1957 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous A, 1958-1959 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - A and C Metal Products Co., 1958 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Abe Alperin D.S. Co., 1958 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Acme Textile Mill Ends Co., 1958 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Addressograph-Multigraph Corp., 1958 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - American Cotton Manufacturers Institute, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - American Floor Mch. Co., 1958 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - American Pigment Corp., 1958 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - American Society for Testing Materials, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 13)